<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Oak Knoll Neighborhood Improvement Association on OKNIA.org</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Oak Knoll Neighborhood Improvement Association on OKNIA.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:05:57 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Board</title>
      <link>/board/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Jul 2024 10:15:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/board/</guid>
      <description>Oak Knoll Aijay Adams, Secretary Rebecca Palm-Song Eastmont Hills Ike Arum Pamm Baker Art Clark King Estate Marshall Hasbrouck, Interim Chair Tamara Torrey, Vice-Chair </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>In 1982, OKNIA consolidated two pre-existing, non-chartered organizations to the north and south of what is now the Glenn W. Daniel/King Estates Open Space Park (KEOS) in order to protect the land from development. The eastern slope, between Howard School and King Estates school, was an existing City of Oakland park established in the early ‘60s. However the vast majority of land was privately owned. A land trust acquired it and held it until the City could purchase it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boundaries</title>
      <link>/boundaries/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/boundaries/</guid>
      <description>
Oak Knoll Alcala Avenue Blandon Road Calandria Avenue Castlewood Street Crest Avenue (9150-9201) Encina Avenue Encina Way Flintridge Avenue Fontaine Street (8800 - 9160) Glenly Road Golf Links Road (9617 - 8500) Granada Avenue Las Vegas Street Margarita Avenue Mirasol Avenue Murrillo Avenue Oak Knoll Blvd Sarazen Avenue Eastmont Hills 82nd Avenue (2906 - 3427) Aster Avenue Cosgrave Avenue El Monte Avenue Golf Links Road (8214 - 8491) Lamp (3409) Michigan Avenue Ney Avenue (8201 - 8505) Outlook Avenue (8201 - 8430) Partridge (3201 - 3361) Sunkist Drive (7755 - 8128) Utah Street King Estate Crest Avenue (7695 - 8050) Earl Street (7900 - 8136) Field Street (3531 - 3632) Fontaine Street (7901 - 8115 Greenly Drive (7701 - 8141) Keller Avenue (3701 - 3917) Lamp ( 3519 - 3601) Sterling Drive (7701 - 8019) Winthrope Street (7901 - 8140) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>OKNIA will be communicating with its members and the surrounding community primarily by email. If your email address changes during your membership, please update our files by contacting us at:
info@oknia.org </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Membership</title>
      <link>/membership/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2023 11:05:57 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/membership/</guid>
      <description>Membership in the Association shall be open to all residents, property owners, and tenants located within the OKNIA boundaries.
The annual dues are $15 per year.
All members, as defined above, shall have one vote each to cast during attendance at the annual membership meeting when voting is required.
Contact information provided by members and others shall be used solely for the purpose of Association business. The Association shall never release information about its members to anyone outside the Association for any purpose without the express permission of the member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Native Species Seedlings for Open Space</title>
      <link>/community-updates/202309_nativeseedlings/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Sep 2023 11:01:59 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/community-updates/202309_nativeseedlings/</guid>
      <description>Hi All,
We want to thank all of the volunteers who have helped OKNIA&amp;rsquo;s ongoing efforts of meadow restoration within King Estate Open Space.
In addition to invasive species removal, this year&amp;rsquo;s winter season we would like to plant native species into selected areas within the Open Space.
For this we need volunteers to help raise seedlings for transplant after the rains have started. Last summer we gathered wildflower seeds, section by section a few days before the goats chomped them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
